<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TarotDeneme</string>


    <string name="lovers">  You may feel unsure about your direction or who to trust. Or you may have to choose between contradicting and equally unifying options. The Lovers in Tarot advises you not to go for the easy road (temptation).

First, gather the information you need to make the right decision. If you face the problem and contemplate it wisely, it will lead you to greater things.</string>


    <string name="emperor"> As a ruler, he leads with a firm hand and demands respect and authority. With careful planning, a highly organized approach, and perseverance, the Emperor can overcome any problem.

This new level of mastery won’t just happen. You have to pursue your goals similarly to how the Emperor does, structured, strategically, and with much perseverance.</string>


    <string name="chariot"> The Chariot is about overcoming obstacles and achieving goals through determination, focus, and willpower. You will feel motivated, ambitious, and in control.

This will help you get a stagnant situation moving again and overcome all the challenges in your path.

Keep focused and believe in your abilities, and you will achieve your goal. The Chariot tells you that a triumph awaits you, and you’re fully in control."</string>


<string name="high">    The High Priestess tells you to slow down, reflect on what you’ve learned, and acquire even more knowledge before deciding or taking action.

Her wisdom encourages you to relinquish the grip of anxiety over the result. Instead, place your faith in the discernment of these metaphorical gatekeepers.

Lastly, the High Priestess figure embodies the serenity of trust and the power of surrender, inviting you to step into the unknown with a courageous and open heart. Listen to your inner voice!</string>




    <string name="magician">    The Magician tarot card reveals how determination and willpower can realize your wishes and desires. When this card appears in your reading, you can be assured that you have the drive to make your dreams happen.

Remember: You’re powerful! And the outer world will follow if you create your inner world. Yet, you have to focus and concentrate on achieving your dream. Get rid of any discretions and make a detailed plan to stay on track.</string>


    <string name="fool">    The Fool tarot card is the number 0 of the Major Arcana, which stands for unlimited potential. To see the Fool card generally indicates that you’re on the verge of an unexpected and exciting new adventure in your daily life. This may require you to take a blind leap of faith.

There will be a rewarding experience that will contribute to your growth as a human being. The new adventure could be literal and may involve traveling to a new land or territories you’ve never visited.</string>


    <string name="strength">    As the name suggests, the upright Strength tarot card represents strength, courage, persuasion, and patience. It tells you you have the power and strength to overcome any obstacle – just like the Chariot.

However, you’ll need to act gracefully and sensibly rather than just using brutal force when pulling the strength.

The card also tells you,you can stay positive and calm and think logically in stressful situations that test your patience and strength.</string>


    <string name="hermit">  In the upright position, the Hermit’s a compelling card. Just as beacons of light often guide ships to the shore, this sage is ushering in a period of personal growth and exploration. The Hermit represents wisdom earned by seeking the highest truth.

Often, looking for answers requires time alone with few distractions. It requires introspection and concentrating less on the senses.</string>


    <string name="wheel">   Jupiter, the planet of good fortune and expansion, rules the Wheel of Fortune. If the Wheel of Fortune tarot card arrives upright, you’re lucky.

Whether you believe in destiny or not, things are lining up for your benefit. Think of surprising offers and new opportunities. Your vision will also increase as life’s tempo cranks up.

The Wheel of Fortune can also reveal psychic abilities within you or someone close. Consider this a chance to discover more about yourself and listen to your gut.</string>


    <string name="justice"> In the upright position, the Justice tarot card represents cause, effect, and balanced thought and action.

Sometimes we find ourselves the victims of someone else’s malicious intent. If you have been wronged in any way, Justice arrives to restore balance and order.

This isn’t to say that things will turn out as you want. However, pulling this card in reading supports the adage “All’s well that ends well.”</string>


    <string name="hangedman">   The Hanged Man represents ‘the waiting game,’ often a part of life progression.

Although we are rarely happy about being stuck in limbo, there are times when nothing else can be done, and we are forced to be still, according to the Hanged Man. This often requires sacrificing people and things we would rather hold on to.

The Hanged Man tarot card wants you to know that sometimes, we must accept a loss for the greater good. Acceptance and letting go are key if you ever want to move forward.</string>


        <string name="death">   One of the reasons that the Death card is such a powerful one in the Upright position is because it carries so many different meanings.

For many readings, the Death Tarot card signifies completing a chapter, putting the past behind you, and cutting out what is unnecessary. It can also signify a transition or middle ground between one phase of life and the next.

The key is to welcome the Death card in a tarot spread instead of avoiding it. What path is number thirteen trying to point you toward? After all, there is no new beginning without an ending.</string>


    <string name="temperance">  Avoid all extreme situations when pulling the Temperance card in your reading.

Although there are times to ‘go for the jugular,’ this isn’t the angel’s message. Some situations are complicated and require patience and special care, even when your emotions tell you to react.

Temperance is a skill; like any other skill, practice makes perfect. Hold back from quick judgment. Resist the temptation to react immediately.</string>


    <string name="devil">   The Devil is the card of illusion. Although you have total control of your life, beliefs, and choices, the Devil card symbolizes how addiction, depression, and unhealthy bonds can make you feel out of control.

Even social media, exercise, and work can be embodied by the Devil when in excess.

Regardless of the nature of your particular problem, the message of the Devil is clear: redirect your attention away from the satisfaction of desires and toward the things that matter.</string>


<string name="tower">   If we had to redesign the Tower card to a more modern-day representation, a crashing airplane would be an accurate alternative image.

The Tower signifies destruction. If you’ve received the Upright Tower tarot card, prepare for things to be leveled and dismantled.

As with all losses, this will probably be a painful process. It can also lead to a fresh start. Before making these positive changes, you must face the truth about a situation.</string>



    <string name="star">    The universe abundantly blesses you (we). We are continually attracting what we desire through our beliefs and thoughts. When the Star arrives in the upright position, it usually follows a difficult change or traumatic event.

Going through something challenging can take the wind out of our sails and cause us to feel like things will never be the same. This might be true.</string>


    <string name="moon">    When the Moon tarot card appears in a reading upright, it can mean that you’re allowing your imagination and emotions to take control of your life. This may be linked to anxieties, fears, or self-deception.

The Moon falling in a reading is a warning in a sense. You’re the crawfish rising from the sea. If you trust your intuition and push forward, you will receive deliverance from what binds you. But first, you must be willing to face the reality of the situation.</string>


    <string name="sun">     The Sun tarot card in the upright position shows positivity and fulfillment in your life. Things will quickly improve if you have been through a hard time and the Sun falls upright.

The Sun reminds us to look at the bright side of things and remind ourselves that hard times don’t last forever. Even when faced with difficulties, we can choose to ‘make lemonade out of lemons’ and embrace life lessons for what they’re: learning tools.</string>


    <string name="judgement">   Now is the perfect time to weigh your actions and see that they align with your values and beliefs.

Do the things you did in the past or today reflect your core values and belief? Do they direct you to your goals and purpose?

Without having the clarity of knowing who you truly are, you can’t answer these questions. Take time to ponder on things before going on with your life. In the end, this will be worth it.</string>


    <string name="world">   To encounter the upright World card in a tarot reading is to encounter success and accomplishment. It means that a long-term project, period of study, or any other major event in your life has come full circle and that you accomplished your goals and aspirations.

Despite your difficulties and hardships, you stood strong and persevered. Your seeds will bloom, and you’re reaping the fruit of your labor. Everything has come together, and you’re in the right place, doing the right thing, achieving what you have envisioned.</string>


    <string name="hierophant">  When the Hierophant tarot card is upright in a reading, it represents a necessity to follow existing conventions, rules, or a well-established procedure.

It advises you to maintain conventional boundaries that are considered a standard method. Rather than being inventive and breaking norms, you will be familiarized with certain traditions, beliefs, and systems that have existed for a long time.</string>





</resources>
